NYSUT President's Office Files. 6174/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Presidents files: Subseries 2
  - Seniority Lists, 1996-2003 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    NYSUT staff list by date of hire, June 25, 1997; management/confidential staff list, June 10, 1998, and January 12, 1996; CWA staff seniority list as of June 30, 2003
  - Staff Agreements (AFT), 1989-2000 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    Highlights of AFTSU Tentative Agreement, December 2000; memo to AFT Executive Council re AFT-OPEIU collective bargaining agreement, October 9, 1992; salary schedule for officers and management staff effective July 1989; national headquarters staff directory
  - Staff Agreements (PSA Confidential), 1995-2003 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    Summary of PSA agreement changes, September 2, 2003; Collective Bargaining Agreement between New York State United Teachers and Professional Staff Association, effective September 1, 2003 - August 31, 2007; correspondence between PSA and Hobart expressing concern over various issues; confidential notes on meetings, 1985-87
  - Staff Agreements (PSA Contract), 1999-2000 (Box 109, Folder 20)
    NYSUT/PSA Collective Bargaining Agreement, effective September 1, 2000 - August 31, 2003; summary of NYSUT - PSA agreement; Memorandum of Agreement, with cover letter to NYSUT officers, December 3, 1999
  - Staff Agreements (CWA Contract), 1990-2001 (Box 109, Folder 21)
    New York State United Teachers and Communications Workers of America Local 1141 Collective Bargaining Agreement, effective January 1, 2001 to December 31, 2004; memo to NYSUT Executive Committee re extension of NYSUT-CWA collective bargaining agreement, September 15, 2000; list of CWA officers and regional stewards, 1993-96; memos re election results, 1990 and 1993
  - Staff Agreements (LSA Contract), 1979-2004 (Box 109, Folder 22)
    New York State United Teachers and NYSUT Legal Staff Association Collective Bargaining Agreement, effective April 1, 2004 - March 31, 2008; Memorandum of Understanding between NYSUT and LSA, April 1, 2004 - March 31, 2008; memo re LSA bargaining demands, January 9, 2004; NYSUT proposal to LSA as presented 1/16/04; NYSUT Response to LSA Financial Proposal, presented 1/26/04; NYSUT/LSA Negotiations: Status of Proposals as of 1/16/04; letter from Legal Staff Association to directors and local presidents re decision to commence job action, n.d., c. 1979
  - Staff Agreements (Management), 1991-1992 (Box 109, Folder 23)
    Memos re vacation bank, 1991-92; list of management employees' vacation accrued dollar value as of 8/30/91; employment offer letter to Peggy Barmore, November 19, 1991; newspaper clippings re executive compensation, growing income disparity, 1992
  - Education International, 2001-2003 (Box 109, Folder 24)
    Annual reports; brochure; New York Times clipping re Ramadan observance by approximately one million students in New York City public schools, n.d.